Anfasa Candra Diputra

QUALITY ASSURANCE AUTOMATION

(+62) 89699141516 · anfasacan@gmail.com Cilacap, 10 November· Pondok Ungu Permai C4 No.11



PROFILE

Passionate at Quality Assurance Automation And Web Developer, Have 1 Years Experience Using Laravel Framework For Creating Website Application, 1 Years At Quality Assurance Automation Using Micro Focus UFT One Automation Tools and currently Learning on Selenium Web Driver Testing.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

PT. Indocyber Global Teknologi Quality Assurance Automation

Apr 2022 - Apr 2023

Client Bank Negara Indonesia

Jobdeks:

- Create GUI Automation Testing Digisales(BNI Application Web) Using UFT One Automation (VB)
- Create GUI Automation Testing ICONS(BNI Application Web) Using UFT One Automation (VB)
- Create GUI Automation Testing VirtualBanking (Terminal Application) Using Bitvise And UFT One Automation (VB)
- Create GUI Automation Testing DPLK Sure(BNI Application Web) Using UFT One Automation (VB)
- Create GUI Automation For Testing API Using Postman and UFT One Automation (VB)
- Following Testing Development From SIT to UAT

PT. Patra Niaga Sep 2021- Dec 2021

Web Developer

Create Web Application Using Laravel Framework and PHP For Clinic To Control Patient Diagnose Covid - 19, Control Drug Stock, And Control Absent for Employee Who Work From Home Because Diagnose With Covid - 19.

EDUCATION

Universitas Gunadarma

Sep 2017 - Sep 2021

Bachelor of Computer Science

Graduate With 3.44 GPA

Relevant Subject: Algorithm and Programming, Web Based Programming, And Object-Oriented Programming.

SKILL

Automated Testing : Micro Focus UFT One, Selenium Web Developer : Laravel Framework, Github

Programming Language : PHP, Visual Basic Script, C#, VB.Net Other : Ms. Office, Bitvise, Postman, SQL

Language: Indonesian, English

LINKS

Portfolio : https://anfasacan.github.io/ Github : https://github.com/anfasacan

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anfasa-candra-diputra-13336a214/

PROJECT

QA Automation		Web Developer	
Project	Tools	Project	Language / Framework
Digisales	UFT One, SQL	Covmore	Laravel, PHP, SQL
ICONS	UFT One, Bitvise	DSS Cat Race	Laravel, PHP, SQL
Virtual Banking	UFT One, Bitvise	Warung Pakde Arso	Laravel, PHP, SQL
DPLK Sure	UFT One		
API GUI	UFT One. Postman		